<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-09-09T11:00:42-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">SurfingOnThe.Net</title><subtitle>The latest news on what is happening around the net.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Importance of a VPN</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Importance-VPN/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Importance of a VPN" /><published>2018-09-04T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-09-04T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Importance-VPN</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Importance-VPN/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/0*G0IA5k9mNJr7Lx-l&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-you-should-use-one-to-encrypt-your-web-traffic-data&quot;&gt;Why you should use one to encrypt your web-traffic data.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@sweeticecreamwedding?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Sweet Ice Cream Photography&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Virtual Private Network, or VPN for short, is a tool that helps hide your data online. This can prevent hackers from looking at data you connect to online, like your passwords and browsing history. This can also protect you from snooping from your government, or your network provider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A VPN works by encrypting your web traffic. This scrambles your data, so even if someone was trying to look at your web traffic, they would have no idea what you were looking at,.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, your web traffic goes to a node in your VPN. A node is a computer that is part of the Virtual Private Network that connects to the internet or other computers on the network. This web traffic travels to many nodes, before finally routing your web traffic to the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is done because if someone wants to track your web traffic back to your location, they need to do a lengthy tracing process that is very hard to bring back to your computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/0*mmMvKFpjDLVQ7-ao&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@rodlong?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Rod Long&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you connect to a VPN from your computer in a coffee shop, even if they traced your traffic back to your location, it would be impossible to know who connected to the internet, because of how frequently devices go on and off a public wifi-network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without protection from a VPN, a public wifi-network could be dangerous. Infected computers could remotely spread viruses to your computer, or hackers could read your passwords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A VPN protects you from almost all of these threats, and keeps you safe while on the go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to all of these features, a VPN does so much more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/0*swrOpiNXsABwJlPy&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@vincentvanzalinge?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Vincent van Zalinge&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VPNs can prevent “monkey-in-the-middle” attacks, or “ARP Spoofing”. This is when a hacker sees what website you’re about to go on, like your bank website for example, and connects you to another website that pretends to be your bank. From there, a hacker can harvest your data, and steal your banking info.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For normal users, a VPN may be good enough. But for reporters that share privleged information, or government whistleblowers, a VPN may not be enough. This is where an amnesiac operating system comes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An amnesiac is someone who forgets, and this is a very fitting name for an operating system. These operating systems run like Windows/Mac OSX/Linux, but they work a little differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your computer is probably storing all of its files in your Hard Drive (HDD), or Solid State Drive (SSD). Anything you keep on your computer can be found almost immediately if someone took your HDD/SSD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amnesiac Operating Systems like TAILS (The Amnesic Incognito Live System) do not store any information on your computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With TAILS, you can plug a flash drive into any computer (a “host” computer), and boot from the flash drive. This opens an operating system that has basic tools like a web browser, messaging, email, a notepad, and a whole suite of open source operating tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, any data you create, like files and messages, are all stored in the host computer’s Random Access Memory (RAM). This memory is temporary, and clears every time you turn off and on your computer. This is only practical for certain use cases, and is definitely not for every-day use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike Windows and MacOSX however, anyone can download TAILS for free, and setup takes about 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you unplug TAILS from the host computer, TAILS leaves no trace.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Why you should use one to encrypt your web-traffic data.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What a theater chain means for Amazon or Netflix</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Theater-Chain-Amazon-Netflix/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What a theater chain means for Amazon or Netflix" /><published>2018-08-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Theater-Chain-Amazon-Netflix</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Theater-Chain-Amazon-Netflix/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/0*s-wNzjqf-5TWF3ml&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;two-big-media-companies-putting-in-bids-for-a-large-theater-chain-showing-adult-oriented-showings&quot;&gt;Two big media companies putting in bids for a large theater chain showing adult-oriented showings.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@jeshoots?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;JESHOOTS.COM&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon and Netflix are both considering the acquittal of Landmark Theaters, an adult-oriented atmosphere, according to their website. Landmark shows independent, foreign, 3D, and smart films from Hollywood. These are lesser-known films, and not the blockbusters you see at traditional theaters like AMC and Cinemark.
Landmark is an almost perfect match for the original movies that Amazon and Netflix produce, and will likely be shown along with the other films that Landmark showcases if the acquittal goes through. However, since both companies are in the discussion stage currently, it is not certain that Landmark will be acquitted at all.
This comes after the news that Steven Spielberg thinks that Netflix Movies shouldn’t qualify for Oscars. In Oscar’s official rules for the 91st Academy Awards, it is said that “to be eligible for 91st Academy Awards consideration, a documentary feature must complete
both a seven-day theatrical release in Los Angeles County and a seven-day theatrical release in
the City of New York during the eligibility period. “
This ruleset for eligibility may be bypassed by winning a qualifying award at a film festival that the Oscar’s approve.
Currently, Netflix gives films limited theatrical releases to qualify for these film shows, because the reward for qualifying is huge. According to Fandango, ticket sales for best picture nominees rose after the Oscar nominees were announced last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*Oar9ZyZ6sBUv6EaozQIjKA.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graph from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/&quot;&gt;Business Insider&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxmovies.com/movies/the-shape-of-water?utm_medium=organicsocial&amp;amp;utm_campaign=the-shape-of-waterhe-phy#bluray&quot;&gt;The Shape of Water&lt;/a&gt;”, a film with the most nominations of any movie in 2018”, had a 241% increase in ticket sales.
There’s big money in the Oscars, and it is worth it to participate. With an acquittal of Landmark Theaters, Amazon and Netflix would have the substantial benefits of owning a theatre chain, like announcing perks, and creating hype.
Amazon could bundle perks with Amazon Prime, or Netflix could make you pay a premium to see movies before they come out on Netflix in theaters. With the domination of brick-and-mortar theatres and home theaters, media companies can perfect the experience of both.
This comes in line with a new Amazon Go brick-and-mortar store coming to 5th Ave &amp;amp; Marion, in Seattle this fall.
The fusion of brick-and-mortar stores with digital storefronts will make technology more seamless with our daily lives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Are AmazonBasics new gaming products any good?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/AmazonBasics-New-Gaming-Line-Good/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are AmazonBasics new gaming products any good?" /><published>2018-08-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/AmazonBasics-New-Gaming-Line-Good</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/AmazonBasics-New-Gaming-Line-Good/">&lt;p&gt;AmazonBasics is Amazon’s generic brand. They sell great items without the name brands. Recently, Amazon released a few new gaming focus products for the people on a budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;amazonbasics-gaming-keyboard-k690&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AmazonBasics Gaming Keyboard (K690)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*XFaOMETc7tml3Hz2BbbAug.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new AmazonBasics Gaming Keyboard or the K690 has a “mechanical feel” to it. Now typically the mechanical feel advertised keyboards do not feel anything close to true mechanical switches.
Sometimes they even feel worse than classic membrane keyboards (the type you are probably using, squishy feeling and the most common). So be careful before buying this keyboard, may not satisfy your needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AmazonBasics Gaming Keyboard does feature the close to mechanical key switch life at 10 million “life-cycles” or clicks. The WASD and arrow keys are different colored (very common in gaming keyboards), keycaps being a silver color while the rest of the keys are black.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 5 keys on the left side of the keyboard going up and down that are programmable to do whatever you want them to. You can program the keys within the included software that you can get either online or through a CD with the keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RGB lights are also controlled through the program. Yes, the keyboard does come with 16.8 million different color variation which is true RGB. The light colors and patterns are fully customizable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the top of the K690, there are 3 buttons labeled M1, M2, and M3. Those are the three memory setting that you can choose in the program. It stores your backlight settings, programmable G keys, etc. The K690 is not a bad choice for gamers on a budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AmazonBasics Gaming Keyboard is only $24.41 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AmazonBasics-K690-Gaming-Keyboard/dp/B073VS6WNZ/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/AmazonBasics-K690-Gaming-Keyboard/dp/B073VS6WNZ/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;amazonbasics-multi-color-gaming-mouse-and-amazonbasics-gaming-mouse-pad&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AmazonBasics-Multi-Color-Gaming-Mouse-Programmable/dp/B073VRVHBG/ref=sr_1_3?s=amazonbasics&amp;amp;srs=10112675011&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1534892571&amp;amp;sr=8-3&amp;amp;keywords=gaming&quot;&gt;AmazonBasics Multi-Color Gaming Mouse&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AmazonBasics-SBD86WD-Gaming-Mouse-Pad/dp/B06X3W3YQD/ref=sr_1_2?s=amazonbasics&amp;amp;srs=10112675011&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1534892571&amp;amp;sr=8-2&amp;amp;keywords=gaming&quot;&gt;AmazonBasics Gaming Mouse Pad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*9uyvT6Ugkt0weBvskzxi-g.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new AmazonBasics Multi-Color Gaming Mouse looks like a somewhat ordinary mouse besides the more “gamer esque” design with a few RGB color accents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the keyboard, the Gaming Mouse has fully customizable RGB lights and a couple programmable buttons. In the AmazonBasics Gaming Mouse, it features has Omron switches (some of the best on the market) with a 50 million click-span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the top, there is a dedicated button for switching the DPI (Dots Per Inch, essentially the speed of the cursor) from 200, 400, 1200, 1600, 2400, and 3200.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*lrx2KX-qSWC_kwLzAb9Ubw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not included with the mouse, AmazonBasics now has a “Gaming Mouse Pad”. I will be honest, I am not too sure what differentiates a gaming mouse pad from a “non-gaming one”. Maybe it it is the feature like RGB or wireless charging, but I digress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mouse Pad comes in a Standard size, Mini, Extended, and XXL. It is a flexible mouse pad for portability but that does not mean it has bad build quality. The AmazonBasics Gaming Mouse is $23.99 + tax and S&amp;amp;H which is kind of steep for a mouse but you do get what you pay for. The mouse pad is $6.99 for the standard size, 5.99 for the mini size, $23.99 for the extended mouse pad, and $10.99 for the XXL size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those were the three new gaming products for the AmazonBasics lineup. Comment if you bought any of them and of course, have a great day!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">AmazonBasics is Amazon’s generic brand. They sell great items without the name brands. Recently, Amazon released a few new gaming focus products for the people on a budget.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Back to School Tech</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Back-To-School-Tech/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Back to School Tech" /><published>2018-08-17T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-17T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Back-To-School-Tech</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Back-To-School-Tech/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;top-7-products-for-making-your-back-to-school-transition-a-little-easier&quot;&gt;Top 7 products for making your back to school transition a little easier&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is that time of year again, and school is right around the corner! We at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.surfingonthe.net/&quot;&gt;surfingonthe.net&lt;/a&gt; have compiled the top 7 things for making your back to school transition a little easier, no matter what school you are going to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;1--ghostek-nrgbag-2-series-slim-durable-smart-tech-bag&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Ghostek-Protective-Notebook-Chromebook-Ultrabook/dp/B074TYB3RF&quot;&gt;1- Ghostek NRGbag 2 Series Slim Durable Smart Tech Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*6xHeYSOO8lqNjLBiF6hFSQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ghostek NRGbag 2 series is a really good looking bag with about 40 L of storage. That is more than enough to carry around whatever you would possibly need. The bag is also waterproof so there is no worry about ruining your electronics or other precious items. The greatest feature about this bag is the included 16,000 mAh rechargeable battery that can easily charge your phone at least 4 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are three female USB connectors, two inside the backpack and one on the outside of the backpack so you can walk anywhere with your phone in your hand, while it is charging. The battery is charged via a micro USB on the outside of the backpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can start charging your electronics by pressing the button on the strap of the backpack which has 3 light bars indicated battery life of the portable battery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three colors are available in Black, Camouflage, or Teal for $79.95 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Ghostek-Protective-Notebook-Chromebook-Ultrabook/dp/B074TYB3RF&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laptop Backpack, Ghostek NRGbag 2 Series Slim Durable Smart Tech Bag With 3 USB Charging Ports…&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;There are many perks of working as a sleuth in intelligence agencies. This is something you have learnt from your…&lt;/em&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;2-sennheiser-hd-440-around-ear-bluetooth-wireless-headphones-hd-440-bt&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Sennheiser-HD-4-40-Headphones-BT/dp/B01MSZSJE9&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sennheiser HD 4.40 Around Ear Bluetooth Wireless Headphones (HD 4.40 BT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*n5s9X479Es9U9UylHEJsIA.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a nut in audio, you probably know the name Sennheiser. Even if you are not, you may have heard of them. If you have not, Sennheiser is up there with some of the best audio brands such as B&amp;amp;O and Audio Technica. The Sennheiser HD 4.40 wireless headphones connect via Bluetooth or AUX cable which is included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery life is a gracious 25 hours of playtime so you can jam out to your tunes all day and night. The battery charges with an included micro USB cable. The “around ear” design might be uncomfortable for people with larger ears but the pads should either cover your ears or sit on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HD 4.40s do not have active noise canceling (real noise canceling) but they do have passive noise canceling (the design of the headphones keep sound in and keep outside sounds out).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a minimalist design, the Sennheiser HD 4.40 Headphones are $99.95 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Sennheiser-HD-4-40-Headphones-BT/dp/B01MSZSJE9&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sennheiser HD 4.40 Around Ear Bluetooth Wireless Headphones (HD 4.40 BT)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The HD 4.40 BT is a wireless headset employing Bluetooth 4.0 and aptX technologies to deliver exceptional wireless…&lt;/em&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;3-sony-mdrxb50ap-extra-bass-earbud-headset-black&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Sony-MDRXB50AP-Extra-Earbud-Headset/dp/B00JRD13T8&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sony MDRXB50AP Extra Bass Earbud Headset (Black)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*iOSBDq_fgZVj13NxTeCR4w.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These earbuds may look like just regular earbuds, but they pack a punch! Extra bass brings your music to another level with high-energy neodymium magnets for a powerful sound. These wired earbuds are lightweight, with a tangle-free y-type flat cord with a volume slider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These come in black, blue, and red for $30.00 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Sony-MDRXB50AP-Extra-Earbud-Headset/dp/B00JRD13T8&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Sony-MDRXB50AP-Extra-Earbud-Headset/dp/B00JRD13T8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;4-yemenren-8gb-sound-audio-recorder&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Activated-Recorder-Yemenren-Dictaphone-Rechargeable/dp/B07BMZPJRW&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yemenren 8GB Sound Audio Recorder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*o380Sm4fmtQmys9bgqjmPw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When sitting in a lecture hall, sometimes the professor can talk too fast, or you might miss something. With a sound audio recorder like this one, you can write more thorough notes, and make sure that you’re not missing anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you buy one, make sure that the University that you go to doesn’t already record lectures, and that you are allowed to record your professors. With this audio recorder, just plug it into your PC/MAC and drag the audio files over. This comes with 15–18 hours of recording on one charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This goes for $29.80 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Activated-Recorder-Yemenren-Dictaphone-Rechargeable/dp/B07BMZPJRW&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Activated-Recorder-Yemenren-Dictaphone-Rechargeable/dp/B07BMZPJRW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;5--seagate-expansion-4tb-portable-external-hard-drive-usb-30-stea4000400--amazonbasics-external-hard-drive-case-bundle&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5-&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Seagate-Expansion-Portable-External-STEA2000400/dp/B01M11D0WI&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seagate Expansion 4TB Portable External Hard Drive USB 3.0 (STEA4000400) &amp;amp; AmazonBasics External Hard Drive Case Bundle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*HuMHsa-P-ScZ7ES3HYrLvw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping a backup of your classwork is a must, and with the Seagate Expansion 4TB Portable External Hard Drive, you can keep your classwork safe and secure. With a focus on portability and general ruggedness, this drive is bundled with a case to keep the drive safe. The drive has fast file transfer speeds, using the USB 3.0 standard. You can expect veteran quality from Seagate because they have been in the business for over 40 years! In addition to your classwork, 4TB can keep all of your personal files with ease. At $100 + tax and S&amp;amp;H, this combo is a steal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Seagate-Expansion-Portable-External-STEA2000400/dp/B01M11D0WI&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Seagate-Expansion-Portable-External-STEA2000400/dp/B01M11D0WI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;6-asus-vivobook-f510ua-fhd-laptop-intel-core-i58250u-8gb-ram-1tb-hdd-usb-c-nanoedge-display-fingerprint-windows-10-star-gray-f510ua-ah51&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VivoBook-i5-8250U-NanoEdge-Fingerprint-F510UA-AH51/dp/B0762S8PYM&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ASUS VivoBook F510UA FHD Laptop, Intel Core i5–8250U, 8GB RAM, 1TB HDD, USB-C, NanoEdge Display, Fingerprint, Windows 10, Star Gray (F510UA-AH51)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*P3GqwNxP_Plq79DyIM6lsw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ASUS VivoBook is one of the best budget laptops out there. A powerful 8th generation Intel Core i5–8250U powers programs like Adobe Photoshop &amp;amp; Illustrator easily. The beefy processor is 1.6GHz with a turbo up to 3.4Ghz. With an 80% screen-to-body ratio and a sleek 0.8” thin footprint, this laptop is super powerful. A huge 15.6” anti-glare HD display, bundled with ASUS Splendid software makes the screen one of the best parts of the laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8GB of DDR4 RAM and a 1TB HDD will power both your classwork and AAA games. This laptop has USB 3.1 Type C connection and 2 USB Ports, with an HDMI for audio/video output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One super impressive part of this laptop is its built-in fingerprint sensor. This sensor can be used for logging in, shopping, authentication, and more! For a work laptop, this is the best price to performance ratio that we’ve seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This laptop is available for $509.99+ tax and S&amp;amp;H, or $102/mo./5mo, a pricing plan fit for college students on a tight budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VivoBook-i5-8250U-NanoEdge-Fingerprint-F510UA-AH51/dp/B0762S8PYM&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/VivoBook-i5-8250U-NanoEdge-Fingerprint-F510UA-AH51/dp/B0762S8PYM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;7-essential-phone-128-gb-unlocked-with-full-display-dual-camera&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Essential-Phone-Unlocked-Display-Camera/dp/B074BWGRKH&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Phone 128 GB Unlocked with Full Display, Dual Camera&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*Hxc3sGzrRVTUaMgXtPLjsg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Essential Phone was released on May 30rd, 2017 to be a very sleek and modern. It ran stock Android, the only other phone that does besides the Google Pixel. The problem was the phone had too many bugs and could not keep up performance wise with other flagships. For the steep price of $699, I can see why the Essential phone did not do too well. But the price has been lowered to a jaw dropping $344.87! Enough about the history, let’s talk about the phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where to start with the Essential Phone. The screen is tucked all the way to the top with a little camera bump that is really unintrusive. The screen is also touching the two sides to almost make a full screen front besides the chin on the bottom. The build is made of titanium which is used to replace bones or build planes! The back is ceramic and the screen has the outstanding Gorilla Glass 5. This phone is really durable and with a great look. Going onto the back of the Essential Phone, it features 2 13 megapixel cameras that can take 4K video at 30fps. The front facing camera is a standard 8 megapixel sensor. There is a fingerprint sensor on the back below the cameras. You will never run out of storage with an astounding 128GB standard on the phone and with 4GB of RAM and a Qualcomm Snapdragon 835, you are getting close to flagship performance. The phone is IP65 water resistant and with an “all day battery life” you can really take this phone on adventures! This phone is just an amazing phone and if I were in the market for a phone, no matter the budget, I would choose this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Essential-Phone-Unlocked-Display-Camera/dp/B074BWGRKH&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Essential-Phone-Unlocked-Display-Camera/dp/B074BWGRKH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was our round-up of the best back-to-school tech items. Please comment if you bought one of these items and of course, have a great day and school year!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Top 7 products for making your back to school transition a little easier</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Should you use Ad-Blocking Software?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Should-you-use-Adblocking-Software/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Should you use Ad-Blocking Software?" /><published>2018-08-16T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Should-you-use-Adblocking-Software</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Should-you-use-Adblocking-Software/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1000/1*v2RmGnII_4rr1lLzSw3FWw.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web-capture taken on 8/16/2018 of &lt;a href=&quot;https://acceptableads.com/en/&quot;&gt;https://acceptableads.com/en/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pros-and-cons-of-using-some-of-the-most-popular-extensions-in-the-chrome-webstore&quot;&gt;Pros and cons of using some of the most popular extensions in the chrome webstore.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Websites rely on ad revenue to survive. They do this by opening ad-spots on their website, and allowing advertisers to pay for a spot. However, with the rise of ad-blockers, many websites are putting their content behind paywalls to help fund their content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ad-blockers block scripts that serves ads to consumers, and end-users get an ad-free experience. Websites can detect when this happens, and some can give you messages to disable your ad-blocker, or restrict you from the site altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many good reasons on why you should use an ad-blocker. Online ads try to give you a personalized experience. Trackers get info about what websites you have been on, how long you have been on them, and what you did on the websites. The info gets sent back to advertisers where they serve ads that relate to what you were doing. For example, if you looked at a product on amazon, similar products may be advertised to you later on, when you go on a different website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some ads “fingerprint” your web browser. This fingerprinting takes a combination of your system and browser info like what hardware your running, and your browser version. Then, when you are seen on another website with the same fingerprint, advertisers are almost certain that you are the same person, because there is a very low chance that two machines have the same fingerprint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can try to opt-out of personalized ads, but it is very hard to do so. There are many ad providers, like Google Adsense, Adsterra Network, Media.net, and more! Most of the time, you will need to opt-out of personalized ads for all of these networks separately, which can take days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One alternative to these opt outs, are sending out a “Do-Not-Track” request. These requests can be enabled in most modern browsers. This sends out a request every time you load a page for websites to stop tracking you. However, since this is a request, this can be ignored. When it is ignored, it is mostly by a website operator that doesn’t know how to interpret a “Do-Not-Track” request, or a malicious tracker that decides to ignore your request anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These malicious ads can serve viruses, and overlay over existing ads. The main way you see malicious ads are if you are on a bad website, or if you have mistakenly downloaded a malicious extension from a website, or an ad served by a non-malicious website. This means that even good websites and good ad-networks can still serve you bad ads!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, as I said in the beginning, websites rely on ad revenue to survive. Blocking ads using an ad-blocker means that websites can fall under financial stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some solutions to this problem have good intent, and some don’t benefit anyone. Websites like The New York Times and Medium have setup paywalls for some/all of their content (in fact, this website is behind a paywall). These paywalls usually let consumers read some articles to try the website out, before buying a subscription to the website’s content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a problem with this approach. If more websites setup paywalls, more of the internet will be closed off, and the internet will become less open. This is why at surfingonthe.net, we have plans for launching our articles on our website, free from paywalls. I’m not sure how we are going to monetize it yet, but I don’t want to serve ads on the site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some websites use affiliate marketing to create revenue for their site. This is when websites offer products or services through affiliate links, that tell the product makers that a website referred customers to their product. One popular affiliate marketer is Amazon, where you can apply to make a commission on products if you offer Amazon’s products on your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a less invasive way of making revenue, and it benefits all parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, if you are still not satisfied with these methods that websites use, you may want to use an ad-blocker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ad Blockers can speedup the websites that they block ads on, and when you are on a data cap, help ease the strain on your network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But which one should you choose?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the most popular ad blockers are &lt;a href=&quot;https://getadblock.com/&quot;&gt;Adblock&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://adblockplus.org/&quot;&gt;Adblock Plus&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm&quot;&gt;Ublock Origin&lt;/a&gt;. Many ad-blockers work exactly the same functionality wise, so it is up to each of the extension’s business practices and choices to change the decision for many ad-blocker users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;adblock&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://getadblock.com/&quot;&gt;Adblock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*wZ4VGSlr6_5uG_ToralnFA.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web-capture taken on 8/16/2018 of &lt;a href=&quot;https://getadblock.com/&quot;&gt;https://getadblock.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adblock has over 40 millions users, and blocks ads from YouTube, Facebook, and one almost everywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adblock is available for Chrome, Safari, Edge, Opera, and Firefox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Adblock is “pay what you want” software, you can choose the price from $0+. Adblock isn’t very upfront with who is behind the project, and they are very vague on their About Us page. Adblock requests permission to Read and Change the information you view on webpages, and to send notifications. These permissions are very standard for ad-blockers. However, since this extension is not open source, it is up in the air if they are using this data for other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adblock is a part of the “Acceptable Ads” program, which whitelists ads from websites that are non-intrusive, and that are clearly marked. However, this is a business model that is unfair, and may put more pressure on websites that host ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems like this is a win-win scenario for websites, but really it is a disgraceful practice. Large ad-networks usually pay 30% of their ad-revenue to the Acceptable Ads program. Already, Ad-Networks take a cut from the same pie, and websites are left with less and less revenue with each ad. This may cause websites to display more ads on their websites to make up for the lost revenue, or put their websites behind a paywall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Acceptable Ads Program does not help anyone, and this is a staple of the Adblock extension, being enabled by default. I would not recommend anyone to download Adblock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;adblock-plus&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://adblockplus.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adblock Plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*HFQ_6ujt7-n4SulN4jie8w.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web-capture taken on 8/16/2018 of &lt;a href=&quot;https://adblockplus.org/&quot;&gt;https://adblockplus.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AdBlock Plus promises the same things that Adblock promises, even wanting to be better. AdBlock Plus has decided to be open-source, which means that all of the code that makes Adblock Plus is available for anyone to read online, meaning that security researchers can find bugs and security threats easily, and help Adblock Plus to build a better product. Adblock Plus requires the same permissions as Adblock, with a greater sense of security since it is open source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adblock Plus is available for all of the browsers Adblock supports plus Android, Internet Explorer, Yandex, and Maxthon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By default, Adblock Plus enables the Acceptable Ads Program as well, with all of the grievances that come with it. Adblock Plus is transparent with its team, and it is funded by a company called eye/o, which builds products like Adblock Plus, Adblock Browser, and Flattr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One problem with this approach is that since the tool is open-source, strangers contribute to the project with no pay, and Adblock Plus uses community-built ad-lists without crediting contributors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, if you want an Adblocker I wouldn’t recommend Adblock Plus, but if you are considering downloading Adblock, Adblock Plus is a better adblocker to download.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ublock-origin&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ublock Origin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*j-fXN9N-MfT4VnVBP-Y8Sg.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web-capture taken on 8/16/2018 of &lt;a href=&quot;https://adblockplus.org/&quot;&gt;https://adblockplus.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm&quot;&gt;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ublock Origin is an ad-blocker centered around performance. By their own tests, they are faster than Adblock, and Adblock Plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ublock Origin split from Ublock.org, an adblocker whose philosophies clashed. Now, Ublock Origin considers Ublock as “badware”, and blocks their website with their filters. This is questionable, but there is not enough information to take a side on this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ublock Origin does not participate with the Acceptable Ads Program, and all of their revenue comes from donations. Ublock Origin is considers themselves not an “ad blocker” but a “wide spectrum blocker”, which ad blocking just falls within the category. Ublock Origin’s default behavior is to block ads, trackers, and malware sites from loading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ublock Origin is open-source, and does profit off of the communities work, but they create their own filters and releases them back into the open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Free. Open source. For users by users. No donations sought.” is one of their mottos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ublock Origin is available for Chrome, Firefox, Edge, and Safari.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ublock Origin is the blocker I most recommend, because of its open stance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is the Samsung Galaxy Note 9 really better than the Note 8?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Samsung-Galaxy-Note-9-VS-Note-8/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is the Samsung Galaxy Note 9 really better than the Note 8?" /><published>2018-08-14T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-14T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Samsung-Galaxy-Note-9-VS-Note-8</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Samsung-Galaxy-Note-9-VS-Note-8/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*BpMD501gQR-W3aMyzuMSnw.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo By Samsung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people were not impressed with the release of the Galaxy S9. Although the S9 is a great phone, it just was not that different from the S8. The Note 9 was announced on August 9, and once again, it looks very similar to the Note 8. Even the release dates are similar. The Note 8 was released on August 23rd, 2017, while the Note 9’s release date will be August 24th, 2018! So, is the Note 9 really better than the Note 8? Let’s find out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;front-of-the-phone&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front of the Phone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*0TCTHz3-rAmsAH9CjY7WbQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.phonearena.com/reviews/Samsung-Galaxy-S9-vs-Galaxy-Note-8_id4496&quot;&gt;Photo From Phone Arena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I looked at the front of the phone for the first time, I noticed something a bit different. It looked like the screen was just a tad taller and the edges of the phone looked more squared. When you look at the specs you can see that is in fact true. The Note 9s screen is 6.4” while the Note 8 has a very similar 6.3” screen. This also comes out in the screen-to-body ratio. The Note 8 has an 82.98% but the Note 9 has an 83.51% which is very similar. The panels are the same super AMOLED 1440p that is a tried and true screen and it just looks fantastic! The two fronts are very similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;back-of-the-phone&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Back of the Phone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*vbvYfAoz9cgdRWZZqMdbNA.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-note-9-vs-galaxy-note-8&quot;&gt;Photo From androidcentral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two things you notice immediately. First, the fingerprint sensor is now located under the dual cameras. Also, there is a colored glass over the cameras that are the same color as the phone color you purchase. Previously on the Note 8, it was clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cameras&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cameras&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*LgaY8UTYbjCQrnMvAyEQ1Q.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-note-9-vs-galaxy-note-8&quot;&gt;Photo by androidcentral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cameras on the Note 9 have some welcoming features and specs that the Note 8 does not. First up, variable aperture. This feature was first seen on the Galaxy S9 and S9+ and now on the Note 9. The two different aperture settings are F1.5 and F2.4. The video specs are have also improved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-video-specs-are&quot;&gt;The video specs are:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3840x2160 (4K) at 30fps.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1920x1080 (1080p HD) at 60fps.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1280x720 (720p HD) at 240fps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-note-9-takes-it-a-step-further-with&quot;&gt;The Note 9 takes it a step further with:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3840x2160 (4K) at 60fps.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1920x1080 (1080p HD) at 240fps.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1280x720 (720p HD) at 960fps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front facing camera is still the same as the Note 8.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*kriw0cyKlyzbDNn0B6kIDw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by Samsung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Note lineup has always been producing large phones. The Note 9 got a little size increase from the Note 8 but small enough to not notice. The Note 9 also gained some weight but again, too little to notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where the fun begins for the Note 9 is the colors (U.S. only). There are four colors available for the new Note 9. Midnight Black, which was also an option on the Note 8. Ocean Blue, which is similar to Deep Sea Blue on the Note 8. Lavender Purple and Metallic Copper are also on the Note 9. The Note 8 had the colors Midnight Black, Deep Sea Blue, Orchid Gray, and Maple Gold. Other than that, the build and design are very similar to each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hardware-and-performance&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hardware and Performance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*PVdklAMHTJgHYMq3IC_2wA.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by Samsung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the S8 to the S9, the Note 9 has a nice performance bump. The Note 9 has RAM options from 6GB and 8GB while the Note 8 had 6GB. One selling point that Samsung pointed out at their release event was that the Note 9 would be the first phone to have 1TB of storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two storage options are 128GB and 512GB. When Samsung launches there 512GB micro SD, you will be able to put it in the 512GB Note 9 to make a 1TB phone. The storage options for the Note 8 were 64GB. Not that close to the Note 9. The Note 9 features a Qualcomm Snapdragon 845 which does perform better than the Note 8s Snapdragon 835. Although the Note 8 had a battery size of 3300mAh, the Note 9 expanded that to a whopping 400mAh battery. It truly is an “all-day battery”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With 38 hours talk time and 12 days standby, this is quite impressive. The Note 9 is not very similar in this category because it has to keep up with time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-new-s-pen&quot;&gt;The New S Pen&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/0*dT2-9K96yluJ9o4c.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo By Samsung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new S Pen has a great new feature that is going to make the Note 9 just that much better. It now doubles as a Bluetooth remote. It still works as a normal S Pen but it now can pause/play, shutter button, etc. It wirelessly charges while in the phone. While inside the phone, the battery only takes 45 seconds to fully charge for a 30 minute life span. The S Pen will work as a normal stylus when the battery is dead. All of the colors correspond to the color of the phone besides the Ocean Blue Note 9. The Ocean Blue color comes with a yellow S Pen. I personally think it looks good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it looks like Note 9 is a different phone, but on the inside. Would I recommend the Note 9? Well that is complicated. The Note 9 is an expensive phone that starts at $999.99 and can get to $1249.99. I you have that much money to spend on a phone, then yes, the Note 9 is a great phone made by a great company. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.samsung.com/us/mobile/galaxy-note9/&quot;&gt;If you pre-order the Note 9 by August 23rd, you get free AKG Noise Canceling Headphones or the limited Samsung Galaxy Fortnite skin with 15,00 V-Bucks or both for $99.99&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Best Budget Speakers</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Best-Budget-Speakers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best Budget Speakers" /><published>2018-08-14T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-14T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Best-Budget-Speakers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Best-Budget-Speakers/">&lt;p&gt;Everyone knows that a good speaker is &lt;em&gt;essential&lt;/em&gt; to a good experience with computers and phones. Say you’re at a party and you whip out your phone. Open up your playlist that you made so everyone can have a good time. And then you realize that you don’t have a good speaker for everyone to hear your music! A party with no music is not great. Well, don’t worry because we have you covered. Here is a list of the best budget speakers in categories from the best looking speaker and best value!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;best-computer-speaker&quot;&gt;Best Computer Speaker&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*xKYLa0omeuRbvAQCZ5EPIg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We nominated the Cyber Acoustics 2.1 Subwoofer Speaker System. The stereo speakers have a sleek gloss black front with an open driver design. Most of the audio controls are on the “control pod”. It can turn the speakers on and off, volume controls and a quick connect 3.5mm jack for headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bass is controlled on the back of the dedicated subwoofer. It creates a comfortable amount of bass while being clear. You could definitely feel it, but it is not too overwhelming. You can get the volume and bass without the price tag. It is $24.51 + tax and S&amp;amp;H which includes a 1-year warranty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Cyber-Acoustics-Subwoofer-Speaker-System/dp/B00006B9W1/ref=sr_1_9?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1533658757&amp;amp;sr=8-9&amp;amp;keywords=computer+speakers+with+subwoofer&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cyber Acoustics 2.1 Subwoofer Speaker System with 18W of Power — Great for Music, Movies, Gaming…&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;One of our hottest selling computer speaker / subwoofer combination. Classic lines, timeless design, compact and…&lt;/em&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;best-phone-speaker&quot;&gt;Best Phone Speaker&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*WFbyjtitloeQihOlaT0Ctg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here we have the AmazonBasics Portable Wireless Bluetooth Speaker. The AmazonBasics line of products by Amazon is known for their quality products at more than reasonable prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speaker has a measly 8-hour playtime so you better remember to charge it! It also has a 33 foot (10 meters) range which is standard in budget wireless speakers. This does not boast any protection features either. It does have an AUX port for any devices not equipped with Bluetooth (AUX cord not included). The buttons on the top only include volume control, power, Bluetooth connect, and phone function.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, there is a built-in microphone for hands free-calling which is a neat feature that more speakers should have. The features do seem lacking but this is a budget speaker. It has two 2.5 watt drivers which sound amazing for the size and price! Speaking about the price, the speaker comes with 3 different color options, Red, Blue, and Black. The prices are $16.10, $25.99, and 19.99 + tax and S&amp;amp;H respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AmazonBasics-Portable-Wireless-Bluetooth-Speaker/dp/B01GF5AFB2/ref=sr_1_3_acs_sk_pb_1_sl_1?s=electronics&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1533687538&amp;amp;sr=1-3-acs&amp;amp;keywords=speaker%2Bamazonbasi&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AmazonBasics Portable Wireless Bluetooth Speaker — Red&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Amazon.com: AmazonBasics Portable Wireless Bluetooth Speaker — Red: Electronics&lt;/em&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;best-smart-speaker&quot;&gt;Best Smart Speaker&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*iPHDghPZ8kXARfqZio_ZkA.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you think smart speaker you generally think Amazon or Google right? Well think Zolo Halo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Zolo Halo is made by Anker which is a respected brand when it comes to sound. The Zolo Halo does run Alexa so you won’t have any disappointing A.I. Where the Halo gets really special is sound. It flaunts one 5 watt “high-excursion” driver with its own bass port!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Halo claims room-filling sound. It also has all of the features an Alexa would have such has smart home control, news, weather, take out, music streaming, and much more. If you do choose to get more than one, there is an option to sync all of your Halos. &lt;em&gt;“Go seamlessly from singing in the shower to dueting while you dry or listening while you lounge”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can stream music from Amazon Music, iHeart Radio, Tunein, Spotify Premium, and Pandora. The top features two microphones, volume controls buttons and a voice activation button. The Halo can also be used like a stand-alone speaker through Bluetooth if you like. You will have to get The Zolo Play app because that is responsible for tasks such as getting the weather and setting a timer. But the Alexa app is also required to play music, get skills, and setting up 3rd party smart home devices. And if the Alexa A.I does not suit you, there is a Zolo Mojo with Google Assistant. However, when this article was made, the Mojo was unavailable. The Zolo Halo comes with an 18-month warranty at a price unbeatable. On Amazon.com the price is $19.99 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Bluetooth-Powerful-Unlimited-iHeartRadio-18-Month/dp/B075GVR79D/ref=sr_1_18?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1533612146&amp;amp;sr=8-18&amp;amp;keywords=smart+speaker&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Bluetooth-Powerful-Unlimited-iHeartRadio-18-Month/dp/B075GVR79D/ref=sr_1_18?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1533612146&amp;amp;sr=8-18&amp;amp;keywords=smart+speaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;best-outdoor-speaker&quot;&gt;Best Outdoor Speaker&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*jjvsNbG_ho5EyB0N7aDWAg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mpow Portable Bluetooth Speaker takes the cake in this category. The body is mostly constructed of plastic and metal. It is rated at IP65 splash protection. It is also shockproof and dustproof. The Mpow is not messing around here. The button selection on the top is a power button, and two volume controls that double as track skipping if you hold them. It provides a decent battery life of 10 hours. Where it gets really interesting is the 1000 mAh emergency battery. That is enough to charge a Samsung Galaxy S9 or iPhone X one-third of the way! The speaker is just one 5 watt driver which is loud enough to have a picnic next to a fast river. It connects via Bluetooth or 3.5mm jack. A 45-day money back and 18-month warranty comes with every Mpow. The orange color is $16.99 while the blue one is $22.99 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;best-looking-speaker&quot;&gt;Best Looking Speaker&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*G4KAYCBH0dYlKx0K_-N9ew.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for something flashy to show off to your friends, look no further than the MIANOVA 22A. The 5 watt driver fires upwards because the sides are covered in multi-theme LEDs! The LEDs do not adapt to the music that is playing but there are different color changing themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ocean (Blue)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grass (Green)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flame (Red)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Season Changes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sea Water and Flame&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Silent Night Sky&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can manually change through the themes or let it change through. The speaker as 10 hours of playtime with the LEDs off, 8 hours when they are on. The controls buttons are on the bottom of the speaker which include a skip track/volume up, back/volume down, LED light controller, play/pause/mode, and power. The speaker does have a built-in microphone for hands free calling. Music can be played via Bluetooth, AUX cord, TF card (micro SD card), and USB. It also features TWS (True Wireless Stereo) which means if you have two, they get treated like a left speaker and a right one. The speaker is $25.99 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Bluetooth-Changing-Wireless-Handsfree-Supported/dp/B079GR96PB/ref=sr_1_1?s=electronics&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1533683464&amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;keywords=MIANOVA&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LED Bluetooth Speaker,Night Light Changing Wireless Speaker,MIANOVA Portable Wireless Bluetooth…&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Buy LED Bluetooth Speaker, Night Light Changing Wireless Speaker, MIANOVA Portable Wireless Bluetooth Speaker 6 Color…&lt;/em&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;best-value-speaker&quot;&gt;Best Value Speaker&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*oO1ch2uh0dcIxZKkJsfcdQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for the best value speaker, there is the Anker Soundcore. On the inside, there are two 6 watt speakers with a bass port in the center. The speaker has an astonishing 24-hour battery! With 66 feet (20 meters) range, you can listen to your music all of the time. A very durable build allows for a sturdy and worry free design. The top buttons feature an on/off button, Bluetooth connect, pause/play, and volume control. With a built-in microphone, this really is the complete package. The Anker Soundcore is $25.99 + tax and S&amp;amp;H.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Anker-Soundcore-Bluetooth-Playtime-Portable/dp/B016XTADG2/ref=sr_1_6?s=electronics&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1533617377&amp;amp;sr=1-6&amp;amp;keywords=speaker&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anker Soundcore Bluetooth Speaker with Loud Stereo Sound, Rich Bass, 24-Hour Playtime, 66 ft…&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;SoundCore The Bluetooth Speaker with Superior Sound and Playtime. From ANKER, the Choice of 10 Million+ Happy Users…&lt;/em&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was our round up of the best budget speakers in these certain categories. Now you are prepared for any party, hiking trip, or movie! If you bought any of these speakers, please comment which one you bought!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*W2E88Om4eNBiwb4wHa5n4Q.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebates.com/r/JAMESJ2385?eeid=28187&quot;&gt;Ebates Affiliate Link&lt;/a&gt;, and help support the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;looking-for-more-great-deals-check-out-our-review-of-yeetcom-a-liquidation-platform-with-good-deals&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-a-new-massdrop-groupon-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;Looking for more great deals? Check out our review of yeet.com, a liquidation platform with good deals!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Everyone knows that a good speaker is essential to a good experience with computers and phones. Say you’re at a party and you whip out your phone. Open up your playlist that you made so everyone can have a good time. And then you realize that you don’t have a good speaker for everyone to hear your music! A party with no music is not great. Well, don’t worry because we have you covered. Here is a list of the best budget speakers in categories from the best looking speaker and best value!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is YEET! a new Massdrop/Groupon competitor?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Is-YEET!-a-new-Massdrop-Groupon-competitor/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is YEET! a new Massdrop/Groupon competitor?" /><published>2018-08-10T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-08-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Is-YEET!-a-new-Massdrop-Groupon-competitor</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Is-YEET!-a-new-Massdrop-Groupon-competitor/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*0aVmH5nfxul2MvcJFuVncA.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Page sample, for Ruffles Chips&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yeet-an-up-and-coming-startup-could-be-the-next-home-delivery-competitor&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-com-a-new-home-delivery-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt;, an up and coming startup, could be the next home delivery competitor.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE: If you join Massdrop using&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;our referral link&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, you will get a $10 credit when you sign up. Links to Groupon are also&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groupon.com/visitor_referral/h/fcd4a25d-3e78-4800-9539-28dab6d85a66&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;referral links&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yeet.com/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-com-a-new-home-delivery-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;“provides a liquidation platform where vendors can quickly sell overstocked products to our customers for a discounted price through our unique social buying experience.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you buy a product, you get it at a “pre-authorized” price. This means that this price is the highest that you will pay for that product. When more people come to buy the same product, the price drops. The price you actually pay is not always lower than the “pre-authorized” price, but it can never get higher. When the sale ends, you are charged for the ending price, and shipping starts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-com-a-new-home-delivery-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; Has products from these categories, with more coming soon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Baby&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beverages&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Body&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cleaning Supplies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Electronics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Groceries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Home&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, please note that these categories may change at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some products are not guaranteed free shipping, and the time in which you get your products may take a matter of days. However, products on this site go for way cheaper, and this site is proud of their prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under each listing is a price check from similar home delivery companies like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newegg.com/&quot;&gt;Newegg&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jet.com/&quot;&gt;Jet&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently, this isn’t the first time &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-com-a-new-home-delivery-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; has launched their service before. An Instagram post from September 18 last year show that &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-com-a-new-home-delivery-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; is launching their service for the second time. This can be a little suspicious, seeming that this is the same time as last year. However, their payments are secured by paypal, so if anything fishy goes on, you can get your money back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe data-width=&quot;1920&quot; data-height=&quot;1080&quot; width=&quot;910&quot; height=&quot;512&quot; data-src=&quot;/media/c9d621ebc597b8fa58390e4e8d4fdabb?postId=45b994382eba&quot; data-media-id=&quot;c9d621ebc597b8fa58390e4e8d4fdabb&quot; data-thumbnail=&quot;https://i.embed.ly/1/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fi.vimeocdn.com%2Fvideo%2F646904269_1280.jpg&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&quot; class=&quot;progressiveMedia-iframe js-progressiveMedia-iframe&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;https://medium.com/media/c9d621ebc597b8fa58390e4e8d4fdabb?postId=45b994382eba&quot; style=&quot;display: block; position: absolute; margin: auto; max-width: 100%; box-sizing: border-box; transform: translateZ(0px); top: 0px; left: 0px; width: 941px; height: 529.781px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-com-a-new-home-delivery-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; has offered 2-day shipping, but it is uncertain if this feature will carry over on the new launch. Currently, the website shows a shipping offer for free shipping on select items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yeet.com/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; compare to competitors like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groupon.com/visitor_referral/h/fcd4a25d-3e78-4800-9539-28dab6d85a66&quot;&gt;Groupon&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; has the same crowd-based buying system like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yeet.com/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt;, where the more people who buy an item, the cheaper it gets. However, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; has been around longer than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yeet.com/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt;, being founded in 2012. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; partners with companies to make &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; exclusive products, which are usually cheaper than the off-site version.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*4hBjMeEMU6x4faw0BdeAqQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; allows you to sign up to different “communities” which subscribe you to deals from a certain topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*LiQAi0hxytUVIFz0ubI5bg.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; Categories&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not many categories from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://yeet%21/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; overlap, and it seems like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; is appealing to the tech crowd, while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yeet.com/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; is in the market for groceries and home supplies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groupon.com/visitor_referral/h/fcd4a25d-3e78-4800-9539-28dab6d85a66&quot;&gt;Groupon&lt;/a&gt; works exactly the same way as the two previous services. However, instead of products, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groupon.com/visitor_referral/h/fcd4a25d-3e78-4800-9539-28dab6d85a66&quot;&gt;Groupon&lt;/a&gt; deals with services, cash back coupons, and vouchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1000/1*1YLRazBwHH0Y3iQiLqXkjw.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a whole new market all together, with new deals and ways to save money. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groupon.com/visitor_referral/h/fcd4a25d-3e78-4800-9539-28dab6d85a66&quot;&gt;Groupon&lt;/a&gt; mainly partners with local businesses for cheaper deals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which service should you choose? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yeet.com/&quot;&gt;YEET!&lt;/a&gt; is in its infancy, and many things can change and become apparent in the near future. For now, I would use established companies like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.massdrop.com/?referer=YLGTTS&quot;&gt;Massdrop&lt;/a&gt; for technology purchases, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groupon.com/visitor_referral/h/fcd4a25d-3e78-4800-9539-28dab6d85a66&quot;&gt;Groupon&lt;/a&gt;for local purchases.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Top Free Things for Students in Tech</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Top-Free-Things-for-Students-in-Tech/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top Free Things for Students in Tech" /><published>2018-06-23T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-06-23T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Top-Free-Things-for-Students-in-Tech</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Top-Free-Things-for-Students-in-Tech/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*8L052mIT1uQieJ5SGzEKbg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-free-or-discounted-items-for-being-a-student&quot;&gt;Get free, or discounted items for being a student!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might not know, but there are a ton of free resources for students that many people have available to them. In this article, I am going to round up some of the best deals for students. If I miss anything, please let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;github-student-developer-pack&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://education.github.com/pack&quot;&gt;GitHub Student Developer Pack&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*eHl3EWODh2NdULv0lmJl5w.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This pack assembled by GitHub has a multitude of discounts and free things. The only thing you need is proof of being a student. This can be a school email, or other identification like a Student ID.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;110-of-bonus-amazon-web-services-credit&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/&quot;&gt;$110 of bonus Amazon Web Services credit.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*toPJ6Uj7IgRLteDZFLXEtQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toy around with everything from Machine Learning, IOT, and even Serverless Computing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;bitnami-business-3-plan-normally-49month-free-for-one-year&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitnami.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitnami Business 3 Plan (normally $49/month) free for one year&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*3XLWEkicpb3E3jV1h-Kyew.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitnami is the industry leader in application packaging. They have automated packaging, deploying and maintaining applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;carto-free-account-upgrades-with-increased-database-storage-real-time-data-location-data-services-credits-and-premium-features-for-2-years&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://carto.com/&quot;&gt;Carto Free Account Upgrades with increased database storage, real time data, Location Data Services Credits, and premium features for 2 years.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*acuzaG3YjukPdEiGf0z7Sw.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carto is an open and powerful platform for spatial data analysis, visualization, and application creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;access-to-figure-eight&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figure-eight.com/&quot;&gt;Access to Figure Eight&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use the crowd-sourced platform to help improve your AI, and make it run better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;datadog-pro-account-including-10-servers-free-for-2-years&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.datadoghq.com/&quot;&gt;Datadog Pro Account, including 10 servers. Free for 2 years.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Datadog provides cloud-based infrastructure monitoring&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;digital-ocean-50-in-platform-credit-for-new-users&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitalocean.com/&quot;&gt;Digital Ocean $50 in platform credit for new users&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*yMwIes5UjHtVKLjjbs5mhA.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital Ocean is a cloud computing platform that manages your app’s infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;free-one-month-membership-149-value-to-flatiron-school-online-coding-bootcamp&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://flatironschool.com/&quot;&gt;Free one-month membership ($149 value) to Flatiron School Online Coding Bootcamp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*58auheA_Rqw1FWirykeFCg.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flatiron School is a proven Coding Bootcamp, with notable alumni.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Unlimited private repositories (normally $7/month) while you are a student.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*eHl3EWODh2NdULv0lmJl5w.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GitHub offers repository storage and hosting with the Git file system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;gitkraken-pro-account-for-1-user-free-for-1-year-normally-60year&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gitkraken.com/&quot;&gt;GitKraken Pro account for 1 user. Free for 1 year (normally $60/year).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GitKraken is a multi platform Git GUI client, available for Windows, Mac, and Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;hackhands-25-in-platform-credit&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hackhands.com/&quot;&gt;Hackhands $25 in platform credit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*yh1OayJBovSxvhIVrnJJlQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hackhands is a service that offers programming help 24/7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;namecheap-one-year-ssl-certificate-normally-9year-one-year-domain-name-registration-on-the-me-tld-normally-1899year&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.namecheap.com/&quot;&gt;NameCheap One year SSL certificate (normally $9/year), One year domain name registration on the .me TLD (normally $18.99/year).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Domain service with affordable registration, hosting, and domain management&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sendgrid-student-plan-15k-with-free-emailsmonth-normally-limited-to-200-free-emailsday-while-youre-a-student&quot;&gt;SendGrid Student plan 15K with free emails/month (normally limited to 200 free emails/day) while you’re a student.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*xEyFR6R_zcJZyzUemhyCew.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Email service trusted by developers and marketers for time-savings, scalability, and delivery expertise.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;500000-eventsmonth-with-unlimited-projects-and-members-while-youre-a-student-with-sentry&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sentry.io/welcome/&quot;&gt;500,000 events/month with unlimited projects and members while you’re a student with Sentry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sentry is &lt;em&gt;“open-source error tracking that helps developers monitor and fix crashes in real time.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;waived-transaction-fees-on-first-1000-in-revenue-processed-with-stripe&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stripe.com/&quot;&gt;Waived transaction fees on first $1000 in revenue processed with Stripe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*KpFmVJEVFa5Idc76XxLxCw.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stripe is a banking and online payment software platform for online businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;complete-access-to-the-suite-of-tools-for-native-mobile-apps-unlimited-access-to-the-platform-free-for-6-months-with-taplytics&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://taplytics.com/&quot;&gt;Complete access to the suite of tools for native mobile apps. Unlimited access to the platform free for 6 months with Taplytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Taplytics is an intelligent customer experience cloud specializing in turning first-time users into lifetime customers through magical moments”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;one-month-of-access-to-a-web-development-course-by-thinkful&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thinkful.com/&quot;&gt;One month of access to a web development course by Thinkful&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinkful is an online web development course in HTML/CSS/JavaScript with online office hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;one-year-free-of-the-transifex-starter-plan-a-99month-value-get-50000-hosted-words-unlimited-projects-and-access-to-translation-partners&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.transifex.com/&quot;&gt;One year free of the Transifex Starter plan, a $99/month value. Get 50,000 hosted words, unlimited projects, and access to translation partners.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transifex is an online localization platform for your projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;private-builds-with-travis-ci-normally-69month-while-youre-a-student&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://travis-ci.org/&quot;&gt;Private builds with Travis CI (normally $69/month) while you’re a student&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Testing for your GitHub projects, to help with security and functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;unreal-engine-while-youre-a-student&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unrealengine.com/&quot;&gt;Unreal Engine while you’re a student&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*MfrI5_EJNsaGztmNLrDKiQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“A complete suite of game development tools for PC, console, mobile, web and VR”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;microsoft-imagine&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imagine.microsoft.com/en-us&quot;&gt;Microsoft Imagine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*C2eDid9ohqk4YeNQouyC6g.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get free Microsoft tools, by verifying with a school email or an access code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;microsoft-azure-with-free-cloud-services&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/&quot;&gt;Microsoft Azure with Free Cloud Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Develop in the cloud at no cost with Azure App Services, Notification Hubs, SQL database, and more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;microsoft-virtual-academy&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mva.microsoft.com/&quot;&gt;Microsoft Virtual Academy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“A large collection of cross-platform learning delivered by Microsoft people and partners to help you build your technical skills and advance your career.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;free-3-month-trial-for-parallels-desktop-for-mac-pro-edition&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parallels.com/products/desktop/&quot;&gt;Free 3-Month Trial for Parallels Desktop for Mac Pro Edition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Powerful virtualization solution for running Windows and Mac apps side-by-side, without rebooting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;php-tools-plugin-for-microsoft-visual-studio&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.devsense.com/&quot;&gt;PHP Tools Plugin for Microsoft Visual Studio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Provides smart code completion, quick navigation, syntax error checking, debugging support, an integrated PHP manual, and much more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pluralsight&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pluralsight.com/&quot;&gt;Pluralsight&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Rich collection of online training courses delivered by world-renowned industry developers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sql-server-2017-developer-edition&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/sql/sql-server/editions-and-components-of-sql-server-2017?view=sql-server-2017&quot;&gt;SQL Server 2017 Developer Edition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Comprehensive datacenter capabilities for mission-critical database, business intelligence, and advanced analytics workloads.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;visual-studio-code&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://code.visualstudio.com/&quot;&gt;Visual Studio Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Modern lightweight code editor. A free, powerful code editor for Linux, MacOS, and Windows.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;visual-studio-community-2017&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/vs/community/&quot;&gt;Visual Studio Community 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ A free, fully-featured, and extensible IDE for creating modern applications for Windows, Android, and iOS, as well as web applications and cloud services.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;visual-studio-for-mac&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/vs/mac/&quot;&gt;Visual Studio for Mac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ A mobile first, cloud first IDE. Made for the Mac. Everything you need for mobile, cloud, and Mac development.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;windows-embedded-81-industry-pro&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=40745&quot;&gt;Windows Embedded 8.1 Industry Pro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Extends Windows 8.1 to a range of industry devices and powerful line-of-business apps where security and reliability are paramount.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;windows-server-2016&quot;&gt;Windows Server 2016&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Delivers global-scale cloud services for any datacenter or cloud.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;windows-store-developer-account&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-US/store/apps/windows&quot;&gt;Windows Store Developer Account&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Publish your apps on the Store for free with a special student registration code.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;wintellect-now&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wintellectnow.com/&quot;&gt;Wintellect Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Courses on the latest new technologies authored by some of the most respected names in the industry delivered directly to your desktop or mobile device.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;xamarin-studio-community-edition&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xamarin.com/&quot;&gt;Xamarin Studio Community Edition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ Use C# to code and deploy Android, iOS, and Windows apps in Visual Studio.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;looking-for-more-great-deals-check-out-our-review-of-yeetcom-a-liquidation-platform-with-good-deals&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/surfing-on-the-net/is-yeet-a-new-massdrop-groupon-competitor-45b994382eba&quot;&gt;Looking for more great deals? Check out our review of yeet.com, a liquidation platform with good deals!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>